earn1kaday.net 2018-06-13

# 

                           PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your
experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and
we want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and
opportunities with complete confidence.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm
commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes
how our company collects information from all end users of our
Internet services (the "Services")-those who access some of our
Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who
may purchase Products and/or pay a monthly service fee to subscribe
to the Service ("Members")-what we do with the information we
collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the
collection and use of such information. We request that you read this
Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting our Company Web site, you are
consenting to our policy of collecting and using your data.
Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used
Introduction. Our company collects information in different ways from
Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and
the network of Web sites accessible through our Service.
Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal
information when they sign up for our Products or Services including
name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit
card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access
the Services. The personal information collected from Members during
the registration process is used to manage each Member's account
(such as for billing purposes). This information may be shared with
third parties, as stated herein, or in special circumstances.
 However, in instances where our company and a partner jointly
promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal
information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who
subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the
purpose of offering you other products and services.
We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from
personal information Members provide during registration (such as the
total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more
detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying
information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services.
Our Company collects personal information through forms you
complete on the site, as well as but not limited to contests,
sweepstakes, text messages, e-mails, faxes, telephone calls, postal mail
or other communications with the user, as well as from outside sources
such as credit card processors and database vendors.

Also, with purchases, we supply our member's contact information, to
our business partners, who then may contact the member by telephone
after the member purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by the that
business partner company. We also may supply other companies with
contact information, for mail offers we believe would be of interest to
our members, with or without compensation from those companies. At
times we may send an advertisement for a third party product, where
we collect the sales proceeds, and forward the purchaser's information
to that third party.
Our Company Partners and Sponsors: Some products and services
may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an
affiliate, independent contractor seller or non-affiliated partner. To
provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the
partner may need to collect and maintain personal information.
Online Shopping: At some Web sites, you can purchase products and
services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or
new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to
provide contact information, such as your name, address, email
address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.
If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order
sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information
about the recipient, such as the recipient's name, address, and phone
number. Our company has no control over the third parties' use of any
personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please
exercise care when doing so.
If you order services or products directly from our company, we use
the personal information you provide to process that order. We do
share this information with outside parties that we do business with.
Online Advertisements: Our company may display our online
advertisements. In those cases we share information about our Visitors
and Members collected through the registration process as well as
through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers.
Additionally, in some instances, we use this information to deliver
tailored advertisements or joint ventures. For instance, an advertiser or
joint venture company tells us the audience they want to reach and
provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the
information we have collected, we may then display or send the
advertisement to the intended audience. Our company does share
personal information about its Visitors or Members with these
advertisers or joint venture companies.
By visiting our Company Web site, you are consenting to our policy of
collecting and using your data. If you do not want to consent to our
policy of collecting and using your data you can “opt out” of our
Social Network and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads
advertising policy by notifying Company in the following manner:

Social Network and Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads
(WCA):
A Custom Audience on Facebook.com is a list of people our company
would like to show our ads to on Facebook.com, who have shown
interest in our products and services, with ads we believe would be of
interest to them. This audience consists of people, whose information
and email addresses our Company already has, because they have
already subscribed to receiving Company emails.
If you no longer have an interest in our products and services, you can
opt-out of seeing Company's Facebook.com Website Custom Audience
Ads. Unsubscribing from our Company's email list will remove you
from Company's internal email database list and stop future emails
from our Company, but not from being shown Facebook.com Website
Custom Audience Ads. The Facebook.com Website Custom Audience
Ads external database, is different from our Company's internal
database and requires the following Opting-out request.
Opting-out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads:
To opt out of our Company's Facebook.com Custom Audience Ads,
send an email, from the email address you are opting out, to Company
using our email address provided in Company's contact information.
Put "Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads " in
the subject line of the email. In the body of the email include your
name and email address. Our Company staff will forward your name
and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from
all of Company's Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads.
Google.com Analytics
Our Company may use Analytics tracking code to support Display
Advertising, and enable Google Analytics to collect data about your
traffic via the DoubleClick cookie in addition to data collected through
the standard Google Analytics implementation. Display Advertising
lets us enable features in Analytics that aren't available through
standard implementations, like Remarketing with Google Analytics,
Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick
Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics
and Interest Reporting.
Our Company may use Remarketing with Google Analytics to
advertise online:
This allows third-party vendors, including Google, to show your ads on
sites across the Internet. Our Company and third-party vendors,
including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics
cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie)
together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past
visits to our website.

Our Company may implement Google Display Network Impression
Reporting or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager:
Our Company and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-
party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party
cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your
ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these
ad impressions and ad services that are related to visits to your site.
Our Company may implement Google Analytics Demographics and
Interest Reporting:
The data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party
audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google
Analytics allows us to serve ads to you based on this data.
Opting-out of Google Analytics' For The Web and Google Analytics
for Display Advertising:
Users can opt-out of Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for
the web at
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
Using the Ads Settings, users can opt-out of Google Analytics for
Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads at
https://www.google.com/settings/personalinfo
Retargeting Ad Campaigns and Persistent Identifiers:
Our Company may utilize various types of advertising that appear on
our Company sites and services including ads on third party sites and
services. Our Company may utilize categories of information,
including names and email addresses, collected from users on our sites
and services, as well as third party sites and services, in connection
with the ads that are served. This advertising may include, but not
limited to, contextual advertising, cookies, anonymous cookies, pixels,
persistent identifiers, geolocation information, email opt in, search
engine terms, behavioral advertising and/or retargeting advertising.
This type of advertising is a form of targeted advertising, to the
specific individual who is visiting the Web site. These advertisements
appear on websites or other media, including display ads, pop up ads
and ads displayed in mobile browsers. Those advertisements are
selected and served by automated systems based on the interests
relevant to the user from the content displayed to the user, based on
what the user is viewing.
Our Company does not conduct inquiries into the information
collection practices of third parties that may collect information from
users that leave our Web site. Our Company may share customer
information with third parties to process orders, for third party
analytics and for marketing and advertising purposes.

Responses to Email Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send email
inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer
the email inquiry we receive.
Voluntary Customer Surveys: We may periodically conduct both
business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our
customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with
important information that helps us to improve the types of products
and services we offer and how we provide them to you.
We may take the information we receive from individuals responding
to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the
responses of other customers we may have, to create broader, generic
responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence,
hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic
information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the
quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and
products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may
be shared with third parties.
Special Cases: It is our company's policy to use or share the personal
information about Visitors or Members in ways described herein
without additional notice or means to opt out except as noted herein, or
otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Also, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or
Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web
sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole
discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: credit
agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law
enforcement, or to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic
Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act,
regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to
disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring
legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use
Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate the
Services properly; or to protect our company and our Members.
Notice to California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights
Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to
receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we
have shared information about you or your family for their marketing
purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the
categories of personal information shared. To make such a
request, please send an email to Company, to the email address
provided in our contact information and please include the
phrase "California Privacy Request" in the subject line, the domain
name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name,
address and email address. We will respond to you within thirty days
of receiving such a request.
"Cookies" and How Our Company Uses Them. A "cookie" is a small

data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain
Web sites. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and
sometimes track information for purposes stated herein as well as for
statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide
and to manage our telecommunications networks.
Deleting Cookies: If you don't want our Company's cookies on your
computer, to be used for the purposes stated herein, they are easy to
delete. Simply go to http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?
page=2 for instructions.
Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not
control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for
information collected through them.
Our Company Commitment to Children's Privacy. Protecting children's
privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other
applicable laws. Therefore we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen
years or older.
YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS
THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN YEARS OF
AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE
FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR
USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY
THIS WEB SITE, FALLS WITHIN the Children’s Online Privacy
Protection Act (COPPA) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING
SO.
Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may
disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web
sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise
caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public
areas.
Our Company's Commitment to Data Security: Services and Web sites
we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse,
and alteration of the information under our control. While we make
every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and
systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent
third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any
questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein,
you may contact us through the contact information provided on this
Web site.
Revisions to This Policy: Our company reserves the right to revise,
amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and
our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by
updating this posting. Your use of this site after such changes are
implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of

these changes. Please consult this privacy statement prior to every use
for any changes.
Last updated: January 24, 2016
   Copyright © 2003-2016 InternetMarketingLawProducts.com for
                  Dennis Becker dba MDM Sports
